<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Livingston Institute Teletest Learning Inc News</title>
<link>http://litli.net/dotlrn/clubs/nonprofit/doranelsonaaahm/news/</link>
<description>Livingston Institute Teletest Learning Inc News</description>
<generator>OpenACS 5.0</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 15:52:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<image>
<title>Livingston Institute Teletest Learning Inc News</title>
<url>http://litli.net/rss-support/images/openacs_logo_rss.gif</url>
<link>http://litli.net/dotlrn/clubs/nonprofit/doranelsonaaahm/news/</link>
<width>126</width>
<height>48</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>My visit to Dora Nelson AAAHM, yesterday was productive.</title>
<link>http://litli.net/dotlrn/clubs/nonprofit/doranelsonaaahm/news/item?item_id=23114</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">http://litli.net/dotlrn/clubs/nonprofit/doranelsonaaahm/news/item?item_id=23114</guid>
<description>&lt;pre&gt;Lovella,

You were such a great host. Really, I had such a great time hearing and
seeing the things you are passionate about, in the context of the museum.

I&#39;m involved in so many things, therefore, i rely heavily on ICT systems
(information communication technology) to manage the influx and long term
conservation of information as communication and my own core knowledge
evolution references. It&#39;s imperative, that I spend time with you and
others like you that have something so great that needs to build it&#39;s
capacity and plan for itself into perpetuity.

One the first count of using technology I propose you visit one or more of
my sites where we can outline, plan and develop according to our list of
action items as projects (if you will) that sets the stage for outreach,
initially to your board and select family and associates, then to the
broader public spheres in and out of california based museums.

&lt;a href=&#34;http://litli.net/xowiki&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;http://litli.net/xowiki&lt;/a&gt;
click on login (top right corner of page)
click on register (bottom left corner of page.
fill in the form and make sure to submit it.
you can work on your profile as soon as you register
from you myspace page click on join and drop
you should see your museum as a community you can join.
i created it, after receiving your e-mail.

the system should email me that you registered
but i will be looking for you if it does not automatically notify me.

cheers! We will be able to produce your website and business plan within,
this our own secure intranet. This is something I&#39;ve been looking to do,
have done and will do, now with your involvement.


On Thu, September 20, 2018 9:22 am, Lovella Singer wrote:
Kenneth
Thank you for your visit and the very valuable info you shared re the
community foundation and becoming grant ready. And and the templates you
shared etc

Looking forward to talking w you soon

Peace &amp;amp; Blessings&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 15:52:59 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>

